We have the burger builder project and there are some things we'll adjust in this module. We need to
Temos o projeto do construtor de hambrgueres e h algumas coisas que ajustaremos neste mdulo. Precisamos adicionar uma nova viso, a
add a new view, the sign up and sign in view, I'll combine it in one view where we can create new users or
inscrio e entrar, eu vou combin-la em uma viso onde podemos criar novos usurios
log users in.
ou logar usurios.
We also want to protect some routes on the frontend, guard them so that for example we can't access
Tambm queremos proteger algumas rotas no frontend, proteg-las para que, por exemplo, no possamos acessar
the orders route if we're not authenticated.
a rota de pedidos se no formos autenticados.
And additionally, I also want to pass that token we'll receive onto the backend for requests to protect
Alm disso, tambm quero passar esse token que receberemos no back-end para solicitaes de proteo de recursos,
resources so that we can make sure that this does not work.
para que possamos ter certeza de que isso no funcionar.
These are the adjustments we have to make on our frontend and to make them,
Estes so os ajustes que temos que fazer em nosso frontend e para torn-los, primeiro
we first of all will start with the sign up and sign in view because without having users, all the
de tudo comearemos com a inscrio e login porque sem ter usurios, todas as outras
other things are kind of hard to do.
coisas so difceis de serem feitas.